Anjola Taiwo

No 27, Elet	bu Estate Oluyole	Extension, lba	dan, Oyo State	, Oyo 20026.	090717	01267 ◆ ajest	ther6@gm	ail.com
		P _I	ROFESSIONA	i Siimmat	ov ——			
A TT 1 1.	na Customar Sar					1.1	. ,	T

A Hardworking Customer Service Representative with a year of experience working with customers. Trained in project and time management with extensive knowledge of customer relation and proven multitasking abilities. Committed to maintaining professional relationships with clients to increase profitability and drive business results. A competent customer service representative driven to exceed sales goals and build long-term relationships with customers. Facilitate positive experiences through high-quality customer care and prompt resolution of complaints and issues.

SKILLS

- Good listening skills
- Multi-line phone talent
- Customer relations
- Attentiveness
- Clear communication skill
- Documentation and Reporting
- Outstanding social skills

- System Analysis
- Identifying problems
- Memorization and recall
- Advising
- Effective time management
- Proficient in the use of microsoft suites

Work History

Biology Teacher (NYSC), 04/2019 to 03/2020

Abeokuta Grammer School – Abeokuta, Ogun

- Organized laboratory activities for optimum learning, including preparing lectures, discussions and student experiments.
- Assessed student comprehension through regular quizzes, tests and assignments.
- Evaluated students' academic and social growth, kept appropriate records and prepared progress reports to gauge performance.

Customer Service Representative, 03/2018 to 03/2019

Mk Kimoni Farms – Ibadan, Oyo

Assisting customers with questions, inquiries, complaints and special request.

Promoting farm produce offered by the farm.

Signing customers to loyalty and reward programs when requested.

Handling returns and exchange, taken into the account policies and regulations for the different payment method.

Cashier, 01/2017 to 12/2017

Sunfun Farms – Ibadan, Oyo

- Processed POS transactions, including checks, cash and credit purchases or refunds.
- Arranged paper and electronic payment records to maintain well-organized fill systems and recordkeeping compliance.

 Helped customers complete purchases, analyse there totals, efficiently organised sales record.
EDUCATION —
3.sc Biochemistry : Biochemistry, 09/2017
Oduduwa University, Petunmodu - Ile-Ife ,lpetunmodu Osun State
CERTIFICATIONS —
March 2019/NATIONAL SERVICE DISCHARGE CERTIFICATE
LANGUAGE —

Yoruba , English